<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andr01d Rocks</title>
    <link>https://andr01d.rocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andr01d Rocks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:29:15 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andr01d.rocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Infostealer Fakecaller Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/infostealer-fakecaller-malware-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 01:23:42 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/infostealer-fakecaller-malware-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Summary Finding interesting malware samples can be a hard task since most of them are very basic yet effective. Luckily Łukasz Siewierski known as @maldr0id have us covered, he posted a list of interesting malware samples on his blog. In this post, we are going to delve into the average section since the easy ones were trivial and not worth making a post for. Enjoy.
If you have any interesting samples that you want to see analyzed, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malware Sunday: Android Malware Analysis 1</title>
      <link>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/malware-sunday-android-malware-analysis-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 13:00:58 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/malware-sunday-android-malware-analysis-1/</guid>
      <description>Malware Sundays Sundays usually are days I am more relaxed from work and I like to do things that I find interesting. Follow my journey of android Malware Analysis every sunday (or most of them).
Summary Finding interesting malware samples can be a hard task since most of them are very basic yet effective. Luckily Łukasz Siewierski known as @maldr0id have us covered, he posted a list of interesting malware samples on his blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up a Malware Analysis Environment</title>
      <link>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/setting-up-a-malware-analysis-env/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 03:22:59 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andr01d.rocks/malware-analysis/setting-up-a-malware-analysis-env/</guid>
      <description>Summary This is not meant to be a step by step tutorial rather I wanted to make a good listing of the most useful tools I am using daily for malware analysis. In order to do malware analysis on android we only need 3+1 things. A computer, right tools, a malware sample (and brains). In this post I will help you setup a malware analysis Virtual Machine with all essential tools to get you started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://andr01d.rocks/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 01:39:49 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andr01d.rocks/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello Ms/Mr. Viewer, I welcome you to this very blog you see in front of your eye(s). In this blog, I will be uploading malware analysis, android internals, android applications, and tools I create in my free time. As with every project I do I always start with huge excitement which gradually fades. I expect nothing different for this project but I will try to be consistent with a couple of posts per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my humble blog</title>
      <link>https://andr01d.rocks/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 01:24:48 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andr01d.rocks/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Content Hello MS/Mr. Viewer, I welcome you to this very blog you see in front of your eye(s). In this blog I will be uploading malware analysis, android internals,android applications and tools I create in my free time. As every project I do I always start with huge excitement which gradually fades. I expect nothing different for this project but I will try to be consistent with a couple posts per month.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
